&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那么让我们开始吧。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So let's get into it.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
很酷。
Very cool.
所以我们将首先讨论JavaScript性能，正如我所承诺的。
So we're gonna talk about, first,
JavaScript performance, as I promised.
所以Ruby on rails哲学
So the Ruby On Rails philosophy,
是开发人员比速度更快的服务器更昂贵。
was that developers are more
expensive than faster server.
所以创造一种语言，即使它稍微慢一点。
So make a language that even
if it's a little slower.
和一个即使稍微慢一点的框架，也提高了开发人员的生产力。
And a framework that even it's a little
slower, increases developer productivity.
因为你可以把你打算花在十个工程师身上的钱寄出去，
Because you can send the money you were
gonna spend on ten more engineers,
把这东西弄出去，然后买一台更强大的服务器。
to get this thing out the door,
and buy a beefier server.
这是一种哲学。
That's a philosophy.
它不适用于客户端应用程序，
It doesn't work for
client-side applications,
因为我们不能给所有的客户都买新电脑。
because we can't buy all of
our customers new computers.
就像这里，各位，这里有一个奇特的Mac Book Pro。
Like here, everyone,
here's a fancy Mac Book Pro.
给你，我不想解决我自己的性能问题。
Here you go, I don't wanna solve
my own performance issues.
我的意思是你可以这么做，但这可能不是个好主意，
I mean you could do that, but
that's probably not a good idea,
这可能不是一种继续经营的方式。
that's probably not a way
to stay in business.
所以我们必须考虑这些事情。
So we have to think about these things.
我们可以压缩资产。
We can compress assets.
我们可以减少延迟。
We can reduce latency.
但是这个应用程序最终需要运行和构建，并且
But this application's eventually
going to need to be run and built, and
你不能控制它运行的计算机。
you don't get to control,
the computer that it's run on.
所以我们，作为前端工程师，
So we, as Front-End Engineers,
不幸的是，不得不承受这种考虑绩效的负担，
unfortunately, have to bear this
burden of thinking about performance,
因为我们买不到更快的服务器和更强大的机器。
because we can't buy faster servers and
beefier machines.
所以在我给你展示一个网页的大小之前，作为一个整体，
So before I showed you just
the size of a webpage, as a whole,
我们发送的JavaScript的大小也在增长
the size of the JavaScript that
we're sending, is also growing
非常大的比率，对，手机上的500%。
at a very large rate,
right, 500% on mobile.
问题是，有一种哲学，嗯，
The problem is,
there's a philosophy, well,
如果我加入额外的JavaScript Meg
if I chip in an extra meg of JavaScript,
如果我少包含一个JPEG，那应该是相同的，对吧？
if I include one less JPEG,
that should be the same, right?
你只是想要一些。
You just want some of those.
问题是，再一次，JPEG，你把它显示在屏幕上。
The problem is, again,
JPEG, you show it onscreen.
JavaScript，您需要解析和编译它，并且
JavaScript, you need to parse and
compile it, and
在许多应用程序中，这实际上是这里的罪魁祸首。
in a lot of applications,
that's actually the big culprit here.
这是我工作的应用程序。
This is the application I work on.
有几件事需要注意。
There's a few things to notice.
这是加载编辑器，我之前在截图中给你看过的。
This is loading the editor, that I
showed you in that screenshot earlier.
在左下角，
Down in the lower left hand corner,
您可以看到浏览器大部分时间都在哪里。
you can see where the browser
spent most of the time.
那个细小的蓝色条纹正在加载。
That thin little blue stripe is loading.
现在，我在丹佛。
Now, I was in Denver.
数据中心在芝加哥，距离不远。
The data center is in Chicago,
it's not that far to get.
如果我在澳大利亚，或者班加罗尔，或者伦敦，这将是非常不同的。
This would be very different if I was
in Australia, or Bangalore, or London.
但是我离服务器不是太远，这里可能会更近。
But I was not too far from the servers,
it would probably even be closer here.
我花了大部分时间编写脚本，这就是解析和
I spent the majority of the time
scripting, which is parsing and
编译Java脚本。
compiling the Java Script.
还有一点渲染，沿着这些线条画东西。
And a little bit of rendering,
painting stuff along those lines.
顶部的另一部分基本上是CPU在任何给定点所做的事情。
The other part at the top, is basically
what the CPU was doing at any given point.
所以你可以看到黄色正在解析JavaScript，
So you can see that the yellow
is parsing JavaScript,
如果你看下面的饼图，它并不像，哇，
which if you look at the pie chart
down below it's not like, wow,
我不敢相信这两个有很大的不同。
I can't believe that
these are very different.
它们是相对相同的东西。
They're relatively the same thing.
这是很多时候被称为黄色的大鼻涕虫。
And this is a lot of the times
called the big yellow slug.
如果你像Create React应用程序那样做，并且应用程序中没有任何内容
If you do it like a create react app,
and nothing in the application watch and
稍后再看这个。
see this later.
就像你还是会得到一定数量的这个一样，
Like you're still gonna get
a certain amount of this,
因为我们要发送一个JavaScript应用程序。
cuz we're sending
a JavaScript application.
最初，HTML中没有任何内容。
There's nothing in the HTML, originally.
我们发送这个JavaScript应用程序必须弄清楚要做什么。
We send this JavaScript application
has to figure out what to do.
顶部的这些小红条，是我在文学上钉住CPU的时候，对吧？
These little red bars at the top,
are when I literary pegged the CPU, right?
我正在以100%的能力使用它来构建这个。
I was using it at 100%
capacity to build this.
你也可以看到中间有一个图表，叫做火焰图，这是，
You can also see there's this graph in the
middle, called a flame chart, which is,
你已经在顶端，这些顶层的功能。
you've got at the top,
these top level functions.
然后如果这个函数调用一个函数，它在火焰图的下面一层，
Then if that function calls a function,
it's one layer down in the flame chart,
你可以看到我可以滚动[笑]，在这里会发生更多的事情。
and you can see that I could scroll
[LAUGH], and more would happen here.
Chrome实际上真的很好
Chrome is actually really nice,
在右上角的那些红色小三角形中，任何给定的东西
where those little red triangles on
the upper right, of any given thing in
火焰图，这就是Chrome发现你在做一件坏事的地方。
the flame chart, that is where Chrome has
figured out like you're doing a bad thing.
让我告诉你正在做的坏事。
Let me tell you about the bad
thing that you're doing.
有时，它可以给你一些有用的东西，我们稍后会看到这一点。
Sometimes, it can give you something
helpful, we'll see that later.
有时候就像是，不，这太久了，而且
Sometimes it's like, no,
this is just taking too long, and
我想你应该知道这件事。
I think you should know about it.
所以你可以得到很多真正有用的信息。
So you can kinda get a lot of
really useful information.
但我真正想在这张幻灯片上说的是，
But the point that I really
wanna make on this slide,
我的应用程序大部分时间都在运行，它正在解析。
is that most of the time that my
application is running, it's parsing.
我可以gzip更多的资产，我可以把一些东西放在更快，更好的CDN上，并且
I can gzip some more assets, I can put
something on a faster, a better CDN, and
沿着这条线的东西。
stuff along those lines.
但这解决不了2800毫秒，这两个，
But that's not gonna solve
the 2,800 milliseconds, the two,
我花了将近三秒钟，只是解析和编译我的JavaScript。
almost three seconds that I'm spending,
just parsing and compiling my JavaScript.
那么黄色部分发生了什么？
So what is happening in that yellow part?
对，我们觉得，是的，那个黄色的部分，它太大了，应该更小。
Right, we feel like, yeah, that yellow
part, it's too big, it should be smaller.
[笑]好的，这些东西是怎么工作的？
[LAUGH] Right, okay,
how does any of this stuff work?
所以事实证明JavaScript是一种编译语言，
So it turns out that JavaScript
is a compiled language,
就像C或Java一样，它通过编译器输出，
just like C or Java, it is put
through a compiler, and out comes,
一些字节编码器，一些机器代码，对吧。
some byte coder, some machine code, right.
你还有其他的语言是解释语言，它贯穿其中
You have other languages that are
interpreted language where it runs through
它，但JavaScript是编译的。
it, but JavaScript is compiled.
你说，我从来没有用JavaScript编译过。
You're like,
I've never compiled in JavaScript.
我的意思是，你可能已经通过Babel运行它来制作更多不同的JavaScript，但是
I mean, you might've run it through Babel
to make more different JavaScript, but
我从来没有产生过JavaScript的二进制代码。
I have never produced
a binary of JavaScript.
这是因为它使用了一种叫做即时编译的东西。
That's because it uses a thing
called just-in-time compilation.
即编译JavaScript代码，
Which is, the JavaScript code is compiled,
就像在用户的机器上执行它之前的片刻一样。
like moments before it's executed,
on your user's machine.
这就是为什么我们看到了黄色的大鼻涕虫，如果你愿意的话。
And that's why we saw the big yellow slug,
if you will.
所以我们不是在编译它，它是被编译的，只是不是我们做的。
So we're not compiling it,
it is getting compiled, just not by us.
酷毙了。
Cool.
所以及时编译。
So just in time compilation.
它意味着它是编译的，它意味着它是在执行之前编译的。
It means it is compiled, it means it's
compiled moments before execution.
这意味着它发生在我们客户的机器上。
It means it's happening
in our client's machine.
这意味着他们付出了代价，并为我们做了艰苦的工作。
It means that they're paying the cost,
and doing the hard work for us.
好的，那么编译部分发生了什么？
All right, so
what is happening in the compilation part?
我们已经确定这是一个问题。
We've identified it as a problem.
我们要集中精力，每个浏览器都有不同的引擎。
Were gonna focus,
each browser has a different engine.
Chrome有一个名为V8的引擎。
Chrome has an engine called V8.
我相信这也是奥普拉使用的，
I believe that's what Oprah uses as well,
如今，几年前的情况并非如此。
these days,
that wasn't true a few years ago.
Safari有一个叫做JavaScript core的，或者
Safari has one called JavaScript core, or
当他们谈论被称为Nitro的营销材料时。
when their talking about
marketing materials called Nitro.
Firefox有一个叫Spider Monkey的引擎，还有一些其他的引擎
Firefox has one called Spider Monkey, and
there's a few other engines in there,
离子猴子，还有一些其他的。
Ion Monkey, and a few other ones.
有一个叫脉轮的。
Has one called Chakra.
所以每个人都有不同的引擎，他们的工作方式也不同。
So each one has a different engine,
they do work differently.
我们只关注V8，因为我们真的在杂草上
We're gonna just focus on V8,
because getting really in the weeds on
他们之间的差异，可能不是我们时间的最佳利用。
the differences between all of them,
is probably not the best use of our time.
我们正在努力获得这种高水平的理解。
We're trying to get this
high level understanding.
所以我要做的，不是世界上最好的网络标准，但是
So I am going to do, not the best web
standards thing in the world, but
让我们相信V8和Chrome是目前唯一的浏览器。
make believe that V8 and
Chrome is the only browser right now.
不要那样做，那是不礼貌的，但是，[笑]我正在做。
Don't do that, that's rude,
but, [LAUGH] I'm doing it.
所以我们的JavaScript生活在一个叫做云的东西中。
So our JavaScript lives in
this thing called, the cloud.
我不太明白那是什么。
I don't really understand what that is.
但我知道这就是我做网页包构建的地方，我把它放在云中，
But I understand that's where when I do
a web pack build, I put it in the cloud,
它就在那里，人们从那里得到它。
and there it is, and
people get it from there.
除此之外，这是后端团队的问题。
Beyond that,
that's the back end team's problem.
我听说是S3桶。
I've heard it's an S3 bucket.
我不知道。
I don't know.
所以我们将JavaScript发送到浏览器，然后我们必须解析它。
So we send the JavaScript to the browser,
and then we have to parse it.
好的，你给我发了那么长的短信，这是什么意思？
Okay, you've sent me those long
string of text, what does that mean?
我们将其转化为所谓的抽象语法树，
We turn that into what's called
an abstract syntax tree,
这是一个实际的数据结构，代表了这段代码的实际含义。
which is an actual data structure that
represents what this code actually means.
然后转到基线编译器或解释器。
That then goes to a baseline compiler or
an interpreter.
在Chrome中，这些天是一种叫做Ignition的东西。
In Chrome,
these days is a thing called Ignition.
明白了吗？这是V8点火
Get it?
It's V8 Ignition.
嗯哼，他们在这里做一件事。
Mm hm, they're doing a thing here.
谷歌非常擅长确保他们的技术是不可谷歌的。
Google's really good at making sure that
their technologies are un-Googleable.
去吧，作为一门编程语言，祝你好运，尝试谷歌。
Go, as a programming language,
good luck, trying to Google that.
点火和涡轮风扇，这我们将在后面讨论，也不可能
Ignition and turbo fan, which we'll talk
talk about later, also impossible to
谷歌当你在为研讨会做研究时，我并没有变得更好。
Google for when you're doing research for
a workshop, I'm not better.
转换成字节码，由浏览器执行。
That gets turned into byte code,
that gets executed by the browser.
但是等等，还有更多，我们稍后再谈，JavaScript真的很难，
But wait, there's more, we'll talk
about later, JavaScript is really hard,
这是一种动态语言，如果我们能让其中一些更快，那就太好了。
it's this dynamic language, It'd be great,
if we could make some of it faster.
所以里面有第二个编译器。
So there's a second compiler in there.
这个叫涡扇。
This one's called Turbofan.
明白了吗？是一样的。
Get it?
It's the same, yeah.
它是一个优化编译器，然后查看代码，然后
And it's an optimizing compiler,
that then looks at the code, and
试图让它更快。
tries to make it even faster.
这将会吐出，嗯，任何可以优化的代码。
That will spit out, well,
any code that can be optimized.
任何无法优化的代码，与我们之前在解释器中看到的一样。
Any code that can't be optimized, same
thing we saw before with the interpreter.
任何可以优化的代码，
Any code that can be optimized,
转到优化编译器进行优化，无论它在那里做什么。
goes to the optimizing compiler to get
optimized, whatever it does in there.
然后，这就是吐出高度优化的机器码，这是独一无二的
And then, that's spits out highly
optimized machine code, unique to
无论是RM，还是X86，像英特尔，无论是什么，都是在另一端发射的。
that whether it's RM, or X86, like Intel,
whatever, that shoots at the other end.
但有些情况下，你是超级优化的代码，不会有结果的，对吧？
Some cases though, you're super optimized
code, isn't gonna work out, right?
因为我们将讨论的原因，它实际上是无效的。
It's not actually valid for
reasons that we'll talk about.
在这一点上，我们回到使用慢字节码。
At which point,
we go back to using the slow byte code.
所以这是理所当然的，红色的箭头是不好的。
So it stands to reason,
that red arrow's bad.
如果你能在绿色箭头上找到东西，那很好。
If you can get stuff on the green arrow,
that's good.
就像，这就是目标。
And like, that's the goal.
任何时候我们以红色箭头结束，这都不好，对吧？
And any time we end with the red arrow,
that's not good, right?
因此，使您的应用程序更快的一种方法是更多的绿色箭头，
And so, one way to make your application
faster, is more green arrows,
红色箭头较少。
less red arrows.
你们都可以写下来。
You can all write that down.
[笑]少做工作，多用绿色箭头，少用红色箭头。
[LAUGH] Doing less work,
more green arrows, less red arrows.
较短的黄色鼻涕虫。
Shorter yellow slugs.
一周后，这些笔记对你来说没有任何意义，但是
None of those notes will make any
sense to you, a week from now, but
我认为你在这一点上抓住他们是非常重要的。
I think it's really important that
you capture them at this point.